Thank you for watching!
Hey haru eh ugh your chicks
Master, please don't fidget.
If there is any delay, we will enter live delivery, so do your best and work hard.
Thank you very much.
Master's face is sleeping.
Please wake up.
Master, please wake up.
Master, the live delivery has started.
It's started.
Oh!
He finally woke up.
That's good, that's good.
Oh!
What a surprise.
Good evening, everyone.
I'd like to start the live broadcast,
I'm sure you all know this,
Today, EbiJu-chan..,
Due to unavoidable circumstances,
I'm sure you all know this, but today, EbiJu-chan, due to some unforeseen circumstances, we are not able to have any part-timers today.
So, this week,
Dynabite!
So, Mr. Ichikawa of AmeFlash, please take care of us.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Dynabyte, of course, originally came from Dynamite,
But as I said "Mr. Ichikawa of Dynavite", I got a devil name, "Dynamite Ichikawa".
So I have a devil name.
It's not a devil name, it's more like a ring name.
Dynamite Ichikawa is really like that.
I've been in the women's professional wrestling business.
It was decided about 5 minutes after the first day of my part-time job.
It was decided right away.
I look forward to working with you all.
Since you're watching the live broadcast, I'd like to say a few words.
I'd like to be as careful as possible with my language today since it's a live broadcast so that there won't be any strange behavior,
I want to be careful not to do anything strange.
Television is all about compliance, isn't it?
It has to be poverty legislation.
Comment yuzu yuzu.
Glad to hear it. Thank you.
It's coming.
It's true.
I'm nervous.
It's coming like crazy.
It's a buzz.
That's not the word I use for this kind of thing.
No, it's not.
Buzz is a word you learned today.
I knew what "buzz" was, but it's just a word that sounds vaguely like "excitement.
I knew that, but I don't really know what buzz is, and I don't know if it makes everyone happy.
Yes, that's right.
Buzz makes people happy.
It's a good thing.
I see.
Yes, yes.
So, now that that's settled, I would like to proceed with the recording.
Okay, let's go.
Yes!
So, how was it?
So, how was it? Today is the last day of your part-time job.
Yes, it's sad.
So soon!
But you got used to it quickly, didn't you?
No, it's true.
Really?
You said you were nervous, but I didn't feel that way at all.
I didn't feel nervous at all.
Didn't you see how my hands were like this the whole time?
They were like this the whole time.
I see.
All the time.
I can't help it, it's like this.
I can't help it.
I'm not even aware that I'm nervous, and I don't know what it is, but anyway, I'm like that.
Heh.
By the way, you know, Okawa, you only do the poor shaking with one leg, don't you?
I have both legs.
It's like this at the same time.
Wow, that's amazing.Wow, that's great.
But, you know, I don't think it used to be so good.
That's true.
People used to say that he was irritated, but according to a recent presentation by a doctor, there are many people who work on a computer, especially at their desks.
When they do this, people think they are irritated, but in fact, it is better for blood circulation than if they don't move at all.
I'm not saying that you should do poor shaking, but it is better to move your body to some extent.
So it was legitimate or rational.
Indeed.
Actually, who was the one who was calling my poor shaking poor? Who's poor?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I didn't say that.
I didn't say it. Anyway, nobody said it today.
No one is saying it.
But it's not like I'm saying I'm poor or anything, because that's really what it is.
Indeed.
When you think about it, it's like that, isn't it? I was born in the Showa period, but I was born in the Heisei period.
And I'm not "2025. It's not 2025.
It's not "2021.
I was born in the Heisei era and raised in the 2025 era.
Like I grew up in the Heisei era.
Then I was born in the Showa era and raised in the Showa Heisei era. I don't care which one you are.
I grew up in 2025.
But what was thought to be right in our time is now quite wrong, as is the current poor shaking.
The most typical example is in the sports clubs. We played soccer, and at that time, drinking water during practice was not allowed.
They said, "You're drunk, you guys! We were told by our seniors and coaches.
But now I'm told to drink water.
It's like you have to drink.
And on the athletic side, have you ever heard of the bunny jump?
Yes, I know what it is.
You do it like this.
When I was a kid in the Showa era (1926-1989), this was one of the most popular exercise activities, and when we talked about training, we used to do the bunny jump.
Is it bad?
It's bad for their knees and feet.
That's right.
So now, I think it's probably not a good idea for kids to do bunny jumping.
I don't think it's very good for kids.
It's just, you know, it's totally bad.
I mean, maybe you can call it training, but...
But it's very easy to get injured.
I don't think it's a good idea to do this kind of thing now.
Squats?
Squats used to be like this.
But now it's much milder.
But it seems to be enough.
I didn't know that.
We thought we were doing the right thing.
You should've told us earlier that you weren't.
That's true.
With that kind of thing...
I don't think they'll be able to do away with the sitting height measurement either.
It's kind of pointless.
The sitting height, right?
They don't measure height anymore.
No?
That's right.
We still have them at my place.
I used to have it when I was a student.
But I don't think they do it anymore.
What about the young people now?
Young people?
I heard so.
I measured their height and everything.
Including me.
If you're taller, you're shorter
short legs and feet
Short legs
I was said to be short
I used to get in trouble.
That's part of it.
Now it's more like that.
Attendance number
It's in aiueo order.
But now it's a mix of men and women.
Is that so?
That's right.
We'd start with "A" for boys.
After all the boys had gone through to the ah.
Then the girls' "A" would come.
Now it's all mixed together.Now you see, it's all mixed up.
It doesn't matter if it's purely male or not.
That's what I mean.
Let's say there's a girl named Aoyama-san.
If there was a girl named Aoyama san...
If you're the first one there...
She's the first one in attendance.
Wow...
Like this...
It's all mixed up, in aie-ao order.
I see.
Times are changing so fast today, aren't they?
Even I can't keep up with it.
Ah! What? Even you, Mr. Zero?
Even Mr. Zero?
There are many places where it's a bit tougher.
Or, to put it another way...
As far as I'm concerned...
When you're as far removed from the times as I am...
You don't get hit as hard.
It's true.
In the current of the times.
But maybe it's Zero-san who's the most in tune with the times.
Things have changed so much in the last few years.
That's right.
Struggling desperately like this...
Like you're trying to catch on to something new.
Well, well, well, well.
I'm sure things will change even more in the future.
Yes, it will.
It's been amazing for the last 10 years.
Yes.
Well, well, well.
Well then...
I've been reading your letters again.
I'd like to read your letters again
I'd like to enjoy reading your letters again.
Well, first of all...
Let's see...
Well, let's see...
First of all, I'd like to see some pictures of food.
I'd like to see...
I'm a little...
You're a little hungry right now.
I'm hungry.
Mr. Devil Uchi from Sagamihara City
Thank you very much.
Good evening, everyone. I'm Devil.
Good evening, Devil.
Mr. Ichikawa from Dynamite. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
This is the man who's always been so kind to me.
He's from a Taiwanese restaurant.
"Kakuni Rice" at a Taiwanese restaurant.
It was so delicious!
I'll send you a picture.
Thank you very much!
Recommended!
It's rice with stewed cubes, right?
Oh, wow!
This is
This must be good!
Looks delicious!
Hey, how much stewed cubes are in this?
Is this Taiwanese rice?
Yes, I wonder what it is.
It's a little different from cold noodles, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
But it's still Taiwanese.
Taiwanese rice...
Taiwanese food goes really well with rice.
It goes well with it.
The seasoning...
And the soup...
Delicious!
Yum!
It's getting pretty.
It's good, isn't it?
I'm hungry.I'm starving.
Again, a little
Food-based
This is awesome, too.
Let's see...
Shonan cookies mixed with sand.
Thank you very much.
Let's see...
I would like to introduce
Aichi Prefecture
Okazaki City, Aichi Prefecture
Bai Shantan Ramen restaurant
Ramen restaurant
Pork bone based
Pork bone based soup with beaten egg
on top of very thin noodles
topped with an abundance of shredded cabbage
cabbage on top of very thin noodles.
I see...
Yes, so you're saying
You mean you went all the way to Aichi Prefecture to eat it?
Yes, that's right.
Wow, what's this?
Eggs... it's true.
Cabbage is mountain!
This is really amazing.
Wow, it looks delicious!
So this is an egg, too.
Like a beaten egg.
Wow, looks delicious!
Noodles are probably inside.
in the middle?
Very thin!
Looks so delicious!
I'm hungry now.
Isn't it just right now with all the veggies?
I know what you mean.
If I eat this first, my appetite will be ignited.
Oh, yes.
Thank you very much.
And...
And the other thing...
Well...
I'm sorry...
I'll tell you something.
This is actually...
Kutun Prefecture is...
Kyushu Tonkotsu Ramen Research Association
Or Kyuton-ken for short.
I'm running it myself.
As the director of the institute
I'm the director of the institute.
By the way, how many
Researchers
Researchers, that means two in total.
One in total.
Oh, and one of the researchers
One is the chairman of the research committee
Right.
Well, well, well.
So, in short, one person runs the whole thing.
I mean, you're the president.
I'd like to move in with you someday.
Really? Really? Really?
I love it.
I've never had good pork ramen.
I want you to try this.
Thank you.
I want some.
Tonkotsu Ramen is mainstream.
Like "Iekei" (family-style) ramen.
Pork bone ramen...
This is...
There's something like Hakata ramen in Kyushu.
The kind that looks a little white.
I love it.
So every day
I'm kind of doing it on my own.
I ask people for their recommendations, andI've been asking for recommendations from you guys.
I've been to a few of them.
I did the Kutun County thing the other day.
Well...
In terms of the program
I don't know...
like a bunch of demons
like a bunch of demons.
I see... I see... I see...
The horse touch is...
It's a Devil's name in the museum.
It's a term.
Cut
horse touch
If you don't get in on time, you can't broadcast on TV.
I accept it with open arms.
So
I'm a little sorry.
I was touched by a horse.
It's frustrating, isn't it?
I feel sorry for the pig.
He gave his life for me.
Touching a horse...
How many times are they going to beat me up?
I mean...
I'd like to say it again.
I'll start with the title call.
Kyushu
Tonkotsu Ramen Study Group
For short
Cue
idsuitai Där
probabl
Rutter
f
new
popular
such
I don't think so.
This maybe that opening is so long that the bathospa...
So that's where it is.
But wait...
Then cut the part where Pretty Cure transforms?
Chara-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha...
If you cut that part, it's not Pretty Cure.
Well, I'm pretty sure I'd skip that part in hindsight.
Wow! There he is!
Someone who doesn't understand the best part of Pretty Cure! There he is! So...
Musashi-Kosugi.
Musashi Kosugi is a big town that's getting a lot of attention lately.
It's getting really big!
This is definitely the second time I've been down here.
I'm pretending I've never seen it before.
I'm pretending I've never seen this place before, but it's like the story of the jellyfish.
I heard there was a great restaurant here, so I went there.
I went there because I heard there was a good place to eat.
I don't know why...
There are a lot of ramen shops here, so I might have seen it while passing by.
It's a déjà vu. I think it's a déjà vu.
There's a restaurant called "Vulture" and their ramen is like this.
Isn't your reaction a little bit weak? It looks good no matter how many times I see it.
No matter how many times I see it, I still can't get used to it.
Well, it's really real Hakata Ramen, with a little more green onion.
They're a little different from the green onions here in Hakata.
I don't know how sweet they are, but they're different from the ones in Hakata.
And the noodles are thin and straight.
How hard are they?
Well, maybe you know what I'm trying to say.
BARIKATA? Yes, that's right.
What did you predict? Oh, my God!
I'm telepathic.
He said it with a balicata.
And then he eats it like this. And then he eats it like this. And then he eats it like this. And then he eats it like this.
I want a Kaedama.
And a little bit of green onion on top.
Like this...
The kaetama is...
Takana, red ginger and sesame!
If you put a lot of sesame seeds, it changes the taste.
It looks totally different from before.It looks totally different from before.
But the taste is also very simple and rich.
The sesame is amazing.
And then, you do it like this.
Like this.
Amazing!
It's freshly ground.
That's right.
I think it was very tasty.
Delicious!
You know, this restaurant...
I've eaten a lot of authentic Hakata ramen in Kyushu.
Surprisingly...
I think we have an image that the authentic ramen has a stronger flavor.
Surprisingly, I don't think the ramen over there is that much stronger than here.
Not that strong?
It's not light, but...
It's just that the seasoning is probably stronger here.
Really?
It was very close to that.
Wow.
It reminded me of when I lived in Hakata.
No, of course I didn't.
I was born in Tokyo.
You were talking like you were born in Tokyo and you're from Tokyo.
Sorry, don't say that, my friend.
Is there something different about you?
When I eat ramen like this, I suddenly want to say something in Kyushu dialect.
I want to say something in Kyushu dialect.
I want to say something like, "What's the matter with you?
My ancestors might say, "Go away!
That's right, but...
Well, why do you think everyone is still in Kyushu?
On the other hand, you know, it's on the Internet now...
I'd like your information on this.
It's true, there are some unexpected places that aren't listed.
That's right.
Yes, yes, yes, I want to go to a place like that.
If there's a Kyushu-style tongo drum store nearby, we'd love to hear from you.
Yes, please.
Well... those who were abused are safe.
I'm glad.
He won't be abused again, will he?
That's right.
Maybe the third time.
It happens all the time.
They even resurrected the abused ones, but in the end, they didn't get released.
Is this a possibility?
This is called "abuse and devouring" except when you see it in the museum.
Ha-ha-ha.
Cursing.
That's amazing.
I hope I don't have to see it a third time.
That's right.
You're right, of course.
If we get to Cervone and he comes back a third time...
I see.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
As expected, I can't react.
That's right.
Yes, you can put green onion and sesame seeds on it.
And sesame too.
Salamon is 3, right?
That's how to divide it.
Aimed at Koshiki, right?
I'm looking forward to it.
It'll be fun.
Yes, it is.
And the other thing... one of the letters I got this week...
I thought, "Wow, what's this?
Let me see...
Let's see...
Tamamin, Tama City, Tokyo
Thank you very much.
You are a man, aren't you?
Yes.
I don't know if he was traveling or on business, but he went to Kyoto.
I heard he went to Kyoto. I'm texting you from the bullet train on his way back.
I just visited the Kurumazaki Shrine in Kyoto, which is famous for its entertainment industry.
It's very Kyoto-like, isn't it? When I asked about the shrine, I found a tamagaki (a small wooden fence) dedicated to the shrine's founder, Mr. Maeyama.
I'm sure that Mr. Maeyama is probably that one from the performing arts, with his name on it.I'm sure that Mr. Maeyama is probably the one from the entertainment industry.
Who is it? Yugo, sir.
Te-te-te-te-te...
Boo-hoo! Yes, that's right!
Tamamin-san mentions this on his insta-story when he was there that day, and yes, I reposted it, or rather, posted it on my story.
Thank you for finding it!
And because of that, Crystal, the red-bellied Hanshin, is next door to Masai Kato.
I'm sure there's a famous one here.
First, it's dedicated to the god of the arts, and if you take the time to write this down, you'll get a lot of work.
What's that?
It's the place to be.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
This is a great lineup!
I wanted to see who's next to me on the right.
Chris Hart.
He's a great singer!
He's a very good singer...
8... well then... see you later... in Honshu...
I've sent you a message.
I'm sure you'll be able to see how the Dynamite 1 car is doing on its own.
I'm on terrestrial television.
I'll have you know that I'll be driving with the utmost caution, so that nothing will happen to you.
I'll let you drive and tell me... like a 40-kilometer girl.
Well, that's why I'm here... 8... I was just thinking that this week...
I was thinking about this, but this week, you know...
Oh, that's right. This is definitely better. Oh, really? Really? There are two kinds of people. The ones with bangs and the ones with bangs.
I did a survey on Instagram the other day. So I decided to go with the one with the most bangs, and the result was 5050.
So I'm really torn...is this one better? I'm really torn. I'm sure it's better. Really? Raise bangs" sounds like a name, doesn't it?
Like "you who raises bangs". Like "you who raises bangs". It's like a name for someone who wears his bangs down.
So it makes me feel more handsome. Oh, really? I'm so happy.
Well, of course, this is just a person's image, but when you have bangs like this, it makes you feel a little distant.
Oh, yes, that's right. It's just a little bit. My front hair is rather long. It's definitely better this way. Really? Yeah, it's definitely better. It's definitely better.
I'm easily influenced. I wonder if it will come out in future scenes. In the meantime, let's have a look in this studio, or rather, in this room, including the cameraman.
May I? There is a cameraman here. There are two ways to raise the camera.
Those who think it's better to raise the camera.
Oh!
Yeah!
That's all of you!
That's all of you! All of them!
Whoo!
Yeah! Let's go this way then!
No, this one is definitely more handsome!
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I'm so happy!
Yeah, I'm glad.
I'll go this way then!
Well, you know, sometimes it's better to have it this way.
Sometimes. Yes.
It's good to have it the other way around.
Yes, it is.
Yes!
Then I'll think of something too.
Like raising my bangs.
And all that together.
Like curtains.
Like this?
Like this.
And only when I greeted them, I glanced at them a little.
I hear that muffled voice telling me to hold on.
Welcome!
Yes! Good!
You sound like a sick person.
You look like a sick person.
Wow.
Mr. Jeft is in trouble.
Because, you know.
Well, well, well.
Well, then, you'll see me again next week!
Yes, sir!
So, thank you very much again this week!
Thank you very much!
Yes, OK.